okay we
meditate watch your
breath e
we're going to do a different kind of
meditation Chum Chum means
uh problem solving meditation it's one
of the three traditional forms of
meditation what we've been doing is jum
which is uh trying to keep the L on a
single
object and this time we'll do a che
on which is
uh the biggest challenge in your
life think of the biggest challenge in
your life the maybe the person that you
have the most trouble with
or the events that you have the most
trouble with try to identify the biggest
challenge in your life right
now
e e
focus on that challenge of
friend try to find the
gcha that you've been dealing with try
to
locate in the biggest challenge in your
life a part of it which doesn't come
from you
or at least what you've been thinking
doesn't come from
me e
it should be the most upsetting part of
the
challenge focus upon the most upsetting
part of the
challenge and and try to grasp
how you've been ging it how you've been
imagining that it doesn't come from you
and from how You'
beened e
examine what it is about that object
that might be coming from you try to
imagine something similar that you've
been doing in in the last few months it
might be causing that
challenge
e e
so then try to think
about how you
might improve
things like
what how could we do lesss of the thing
that's causing the challenge in the next
few weeks or
so e
okay then come back to this
Ro slowly open
your oh this is a really good
question we're in China you know we in m
land China and
uh the events there are honestly they're
reported by the American Press a little
bit negatively very consistently
negatively
but
whatever there definitely has been a a
different culture a protected culture
has grown there for the last 50 years so
they've been isolated in bad ways but
also in good ways and
uh they're very very sharp their minds
are very very
clear uh they don't have a lot of the
distractions that we
have so the questions there were just
totally totally awesome there are
questions that that my oldest students
haven't gotten to yet in the first day
you know so uh anyway this is
similar it's the only way to get a d or
pen is to give a donut or pen how could
we ever get one to give when we talk of
a Creator God we say that he can't exist
because someone would have had to make
him same thing with
donut okay so you can't have a image of
a donut in your mind unless you've given
one before but you couldn't have given
one unless you had an image of a donut
in your
mind
okay
uh that's one of the reasons why in in
this system
we say there's no
beginning and if someone asked us which
came first the chicken or the egg we'd
say
yes okay so uh we say it's illogical to
say there was a chicken first or an egg
first because you can't have a chicken
without an egg and you can't have an egg
without a chicken so we say it's an that
in itself is a proof that things had no
beginning and
then but you must distinguish that from
not having a
cough okay you you have to learn to it's
like milk and water okay you have to
distinguish not having had a beginning
from not having had a cost because in
the West in Western thinking we equate
that you see we say if it didn't have a
beginning it didn't have a cause you see
uh and and the first monk I ever said
that to he just looked at me quizzically
you know and he was like what the heck
are you talking about you know if if it
does have a beginning it doesn't have a
CL if there's if there's a beginning EXO
NE
EXO with that from nothing then there's
then there's no cause you know you and
your big bang stuff you know they're
like that's no
cause you know something that came from
nothing you know it doesn't exist you
know therefore the universe has to be
beginning
beginningless you know and we have a
misperception that to have a cause it
must have a
beginning but rather what it is is that
if it if it had a beginning without a
cause before that well then it would be
illogical that's not possible so you've
always had images of donuts in your
mind and you've always had images of
pens in your mind because you always had
one before that to give
but then this person was anticipating my
answer well then how can something new
come into being or happen Mark
Enlightenment for
example uh and there's a discussion of
this in the
Abid when they discuss Tong which is
when you see emptiness directly for the
first time so if you've never
had in countless lifetimes a direct
perception of emptiness which is why
you're here in a suffering room then how
could you ever have a direct perception
emptiness CU that's that's a mental
image that you've never had
before I'll tell you my answer I
uh well I think even in scripture they
would say you haven't yet encountered
the causes
uh that would produce that image but but
that image cannot that image is not only
produced by another image of the same
kind that image can be produced
through uh education or the instruction
of a teacher which I would call the
new the new rearrangement of existing
stuff okay the new rearrangement of
existing stuff which would dis prove the
argument that everyone's been your
mother but anyway we won't worry about
that so through
through there's another argument you
know that everyone's been your mother
because you've lived countless lives so
they must have been your mother
countless times but then the same people
in the same scripture will say you've
never seen emptiness
directly right even though you've had
countless chances to do so
so that's a little bit of a paradox I I
would
say uh when you do see emptiness
directly for the first time it's because
of two maybe two factors the the
instruction of your
teacher in a way that you've never had
before even though your lies were
countless right in theory you could
throw dice countless times and not B
snakes Snake Eyes in theory it's
possible so we're pretty
much we the last people in the world
that didn't get Snake Eyes okay like we
here you know if you're not enlightened
yet they count we're like what
percentage are we of the beings in the
universe who who have gotten enlightened
you know it's it's maybe we are just a
infinitely small percentage left okay
something like
that and that you
can re arrange existing images in a new
way and come up with a new image okay
all right that's my idea
uh but it's a really good
question okay that's a good question
these are really nice question questions
maybe we should save them and write them
down uh if single pointed concentration
is a food for the being then I can find
it in many ways dancing cooking walking
singing in any of the activities of life
being a master in music or
alpinism is also mastering the single
focus of the mind is that less powerful
than meditation and why okay uh I like
to tell this
story k r like to watch baseball
you know and uh I would come home after
uh he discovered baseball I mean they
don't have it in pla and uh he really
really liked it first he watched golf
for a long time and I was
like RI it's so boring you know and then
then he got on to baseball which is a
little bit
better
uh but I remember one day I think it was
Dale
strawberry uh from the New York Mets
right and uh he was up to bat he was a
big home run hitter you know and
uh in fact there's a long story about
how R rigged the World Series but I
won't tell
you
uh but if you ever wondered why the team
that had the worst record in the history
of baseball won the World Series the
next
year uh
anyway so st's up Lefty I think but he's
up to bat and then the pitcher throws
the
ball and he hits a home run and then
after the game they they you know they
have the postgame show and they show
that they show that that swing about 48
times and they just talk and
uh it's
true and uh they don't see anything new
either
uh but uh they talk and talk and talk
and then you see the image over and over
of that of that pitch and that hit and
then they they interview Dale strawber
and they say you know how come you hit
so many home runs all the time you know
because the ball's coming at you 100
miles hour and he and he said
uh the ball starts at 100 miles hour and
it's a size of a baseball but by the
time it gets to the plate to me it's the
size of a watermelon you know it's this
big and to hit it is is like duh you
know it's like you know he said I don't
know what it is but by the time the ball
traveling at 100 milph reaches me it's
as big as a watermelon and I just
blindly take a swing at it and I hit a
home run and then
uh and then they went back to the you
know and then they they they they replay
the pitch and they replay him and then
rache says watch he's like grabbing me
by the shoulders and he's like watch
this you know and I'm watching and as
the ball approaches the plate at 100 mph
in slowo Daryl strawberry's eyes go like
this they start to widen and widen and
widen and widen and wi and wi and that
it seems like the what's the black part
you can't tell
me anyway the black part expands somehow
like his eyes actually expand and then
he swings you know and and R says that's
that's aagra he has single pointed
concentration that's what it looks like
he was all excited he wanted to show me
you know which recalls Dr yesi
thund Who was giving talks about Tibetan
medicine he's the Dal Lama doctor right
so I was translated for him 100 years
ago at Nancy Ken's house and
uh and he kept mentioning this thing
called guya and I said what's guya and
he said it's a quality of the urine when
you when you shake it with a
chopstick you know when you stir it with
a chopstick fast it's the quality of the
urine and I'm like how am I supposed to
translate that what's what's it like he
says well I can't tell you you have to
see it you know so then one day he went
to this really really wealthy lady's
apartment and this billionaire lady and
I had to translate and she was telling
him her problems and then she went into
the he said well you have to pee for me
so she went into the toilet and then uh
he went into the toilet afterwards and
he took his Chopsticks and and and then
he goes M come in here this is great
she's got guya you know and you can see
guya you know just look at this lady's
Peet you know and she's getting all ran
and so it was the same with K he's like
look that's thing Zin you know you want
to know what thing Zin is it's that and
he was so excited to to see it in a
baseball player but then he went off on
this thing like
but baseballs aren't virtuous objects
you see there's no
uh sacred content necessarily I mean
often in a baseball okay like it's not
like the baseballs if you concentrate on
it carefully it's going to have any
content in it which enlightens you you
see I mean or which which changes your
heart you know and that's why in ch in
selecting an meditation object the the
classical where are very adamant that
you should pick something significant
that will when you open the core of your
mind to it which is what you do in
meditation you are allowing that thing
to go to the actually it's here
M you are you are exposing the core of
your being to that thing that's the most
powerful place in the world to make
seeds you see if in deep meditation you
are close to the core of the reactor you
are close to the storehouse where the SE
are kept it can be held on the tip of a
pin and it has trillions upon trillions
of events future events coming to you
there the seeds are there in a in almost
a place with no
space and then when you're in meditation
you're exposing that place to the object
so then the object is going to have a
profound make a profound imprint on your
mind and create profound seeds so
they're very careful in in meditation
Tech to say don't expose your
indestructible drop right the core the
core of your Storehouse don't expose it
to something which is not significant
spiritually see I mean you can expose it
to a 100 mph baseball but it's probably
just going to create a lot of baseball
later or something you see what I mean
and then uh the classical images to
expose it to are your llama your
llama's form or your your your own heart
teacher by the way it doesn't have to be
a Tibetan
doesn't have to be a monk or nun uh it
could be your mother it could be your
dog uh what's his name swears it's his
dog the the the yoga hip hop
singer MC Yogi swears it's his dog uh
his root llama uh we talked about it uh
and then
uh you know it could be it could be your
child it could be someone your
grandmother who passed away when you
were six uh it could be someone you
haven't met yet okay uh so so but in
that case you just you just picture the
most holy thing you can and then that's
that's like uh exposed to the core the
very core of your your karmic seeds and
it and it produces tremendous seeds Okay
so uh or emptiness or Compassion or love
you see you you expose close your mind
to those things okay so it is true the
the person who asked the question they
said can you develop single pointer
concentration on other things yeah you
can and you do great musicians all have
single point concentration on on their
instrument or their
music
but but in the selection of a meditation
object your concerns are can you getar
for it is it going to be something
compelling for you personally and then
secondly is it significant in saving the
world will it really help to save the
world okay so you got to find something
which is sexy and will save the world
okay which is your heart teacher all
right
uh I'll do one more and then we'll we'll
try to figure out where the Monk Is up
there I have watched a lot of TV I have
taken drugs in my life I no longer do so
I have dullness in my meditation I'm not
surprised what can I do to explode that
karma when I have done this I feel
defeated as though there is
nothing as though there is
nothing I can do because of my laziness
and purposeful ding behavior of the past
I would like to smash to
it uh you have to use the four powers
right so you have a old seed in your
mind and uh we all have them because we
were all
teenagers uh
so right so
uh so you know there's a an arc in in uh
Buddhism of how to destroy old comic SC
problem
being uh when you come to a teaching
like this and then you you get inspired
and you start collecting new good
seeds there's this Paradox that I like
to compare it to planes in line at an
airport and the it's first in first out
okay we we say that in business it means
like the first income in will go out the
first in expenses you know so with Karma
normally given given normal given equal
circumstances a Karma which you commit
earlier will ripen earlier right so you
know now you have seen the light and
you're only going to do good
things and uh you've got all those old
airplanes in front of the new ones which
has a special problem about
that
uh they have to take off
first so that will delay the the later
flight
okay and if it delays the later flights
too long you will not be able to draw a
connection between your new goodness and
the goodness which comes to you 2 and a
half years from now you see what I mean
it's too long away for you to draw a a a
Surefire connection and be inspired to
be good you see so it's a very very bad
State of Affairs you you come to a talk
you get all inspired you do all these
good things and then nothing happens for
two and a half years because you got
older flights
waiting okay and uh and then you don't
believe what you heard CU you tried it
and nothing happened for two and a half
years and and and by the time two and a
half years has gone by you forget the
good things you did to make it happen
right you cannot draw a connection
between the stuff that happened the new
good stuff and and the lecture you went
to right so it's extremely crucial for
us especially when we're first doing our
what do you call it we're doing our
experiments to confirm whether this
stuff works or not right like you go out
of here and you give away a lot of money
and you're waiting for a check in the
mail you know and then nothing
happens uh so for those of us who are
still trying to confirm whether this
stuff is viable or true feasible then
then we really have to I like to call it
councel of flights we have to is there a
way to cancel these five flights so that
our new good inspired SE will take off
and and then most important it's not
just that you get five good things it's
that you confirm that the idea works and
that's important that's the most
important thing so it's really important
to cancel the earlier flights somehow in
this person's example they're talking
about
cancelling uh seeds of dullness planted
by television and the use of drugs which
is true okay
um so there you have to study the the
the traditional uh Buddhist methods for
removing old bed seats canceling these
these flights that are in front
right the main the the the Crux of those
methods is to stop is to make a what you
call it is to make
a uh what do you call it a decision okay
but there's a better word a
resolution uh that you won't do those
things again okay and you so if you want
to know how to destroy an existing
karmic seed that you planted in your
younger days by smoking dope while you
watch the mother's brothers or whatever
it was uh you
know that
uh what you the way to destroy like like
it's an interesting question you know
how many seats you have in your
indestructible
job trillions upon trillions uncountable
trillions in your how are you going to
get to this mother's brother thing you
know how are you going to isolate one
single seed out of billions upon
billions and and and destroy that one
without like destroying all the good
ones sitting around it I don't know you
know it's like a cruise missile thing
did you see the films of you know they
they go hundreds of miles and then they
like going into somebody's the left of
somebody's window or something you know
and that's what you want that's what
you're trying to do
so the way to shoot a karmic cruise
missile to an existing karma in your
Consciousness stored in your
Consciousness is to
consciously make a resolution not to do
that thing for a specific period of time
okay so you can say for
example I won't watch TV for the rest of
January you know it's a New Year's
resolution that in itself is not a big
deal okay but you have to consciously
dedicate that month's non TV to the old
TV se you have and then it the
dedication of that seed is what directs
it to the to the previous seed and
destroys the the flight okay got it so
you two things are NE Neary make a
resolution that you will not do that
thing again for a certain period of time
and then secondly consciously dedicated
to to destroying an old karmic seed
which you know you have okay that's the
essence of the four power
okay and it and it will destroy
them you can use that for anything and
again there's this added urgency because
if you don't do it soon you can't
confirm that this stuff will
cuz you'll be confused by the time delay
caused by the pre what do you call it
the the previously scheduled
flights all right okay we'll do these
later maybe should have place for old
ones cuz they're kind of good they you
should type them down all right let's do
a little bit of
uh meditation
posting or how about we just
meditate okay all right
watch it
bro it's the only thing in the
world e
go to the Golden
Moon enjoy the
late afternoon just before dust the the
golden
sunlight pouring into the window
e e
look at the Blue Sky overhead to the
window beautiful andless blue
sky e
try to feel some love for this guy try
to enjoy this
guy the beauty of this
guy e
drop your gaze to the mountain
sitting across a broad
Valley also bathed in the light of the
setting
son e
come into the golden
room and ask your llama beg your llama
to come sit with you one of you
I'd like you to concentrate on something
new which is the a very very subtle
fragrance coming from their
body like if you've ever smell the Lotus
flow good fragrance is very very faint
and very very
unique try to meditate on the
fragrance
e e
again try to get in touch with your
station try to
detect the part of your mind which is
watching to see if you've lost the
object if the object is sorry if your
mental state is getting
dull or if maybe there's no l
try
to try to meet
this Watch Dog m
now try to isolate the part of your mind
tremba which brings your mind back to
the object after sh Rings The Alarm try
I I in my mind it's much faster it's
almost instantaneous so try to try to
catch it in slow mod
the the part of your mind which is
drawing the Mind back to the object
now try to bring up try to raise a state
of
n about that
fragrance a state of being totally
engrossed in that fragrance the beauty
of that
fragrance to the exclusion of all other
things
stay on the
fragrance be content with the
fragrance don't seek to go elsewhere
it's
enough e
come back to the
fragrance feel n for the fragrance
feel what a relief it is to just
concentrate on a single
thing e
and slowly come back to this
one slowly open your eyes
uh we'll just do a little bit of the
poster okay it feels like we we missed
something if we didn't do a little
poster
so I'd like to talk a little bit about
uh say CH no you can't say okay I'll say
it for you
CH which means uh subtle dness and go TR
which means
subtle agitation or subtly going off to
something you like
okay grow dness would feel
like uh fighting to stay
awake okay uh all right that would be
gross
Dess uh overcome by Lang langor or uh
just
feeling
heavy heaviness of body as well he heavy
in your body your body is doesn't sit up
straight uh you feel heavy in the
physically and then mentally you just
feel like uh
dry or you could fall asleep or
something like that that's gross
dullness all
right then subtle dullness we talked
about but I think we better talk we
let's talk about some more so don I
think you could just say a lack of larm
okay
and and it's supposed to be the greatest
problem of meditation that
exists uh being on the
object having fixation on the object you
haven't lost the object even having cell
chop the mind is fresh the mind is
fairly fresh the mind is not
Dull uh mind is fairly fresh and you're
fixed on the object but there's no
there's no okay there's no intensity
you're not like deep in the object and
you're not feeling some kind of
a a gross what do you call
it pleasure in the object okay like that
you don't you don't have that that's
that's subtle dness and that's supposed
to be the most
dangerous mistaken meditation of all why
because it feels like you're on the it
feels like medit
you are on the object you're fairly
perky and uh it feels pretty good it
feels good okay it feels fairly good but
there's not this deep sense of
contentment or interest or engagement in
the object
okay why I keep saying contentment is I
think it's sort of the nature of
contentment that you don't need to move
on to something else you know like add
and contentment are like opposite po
all right and add wants to go onto
something else right away there's
something more important someone else
has sent me an email I didn't you
know uh it's Restless you could call it
restlessness and then to me contentment
is the opposite contentment implies that
you are happy to
stay sit for a moment with that person
or with that meal or with that book
and you don't need to go anywhere and
you don't feel any great need to go
anywhere you're just contented and you
and that's
AOG because you don't want to move on to
a second object you're just on a single
object so I I like contentment I like to
call it contentment
really so the opposite of subtle
dullness is a feeling of contentment but
we didn't talk much about
subtle uh agitation okay which is
considered less of a danger because it's
much less
frequent
okay and that's I think up here
somewhere I think they said here uh
opposite 17 between 17 and 19 the monkey
is is see the monkey's almost pretty
much white before the mon before the
elephant gets
there I think they made some point up
here that subtle agit
right it was easier to
remove that and that's why the little
monkeys is getting more more wider
faster than the elephant okay because
subtle agitation relatively easier to
deal with and less frequent than subtle
donors then I like how they describe
subtle agitation in the scriptures they
say it's like a stream that has frozen
over and then water is water is Flowing
under the ice they call the word for
subtle uh agitation is water under the
ice okay stream water under the ice and
what that means is uh and I mentioned it
in Phoenix when we talked about it
um there's a very beautiful word in
tibetan that you should learn if you're
learning Tibetan it's a difficult word
and it's just simply k k h a d uh K it's
probably related to a word for
cracks
K
uh but K means just about to happen so
like Jun means it's just about to happen
d means on the ver it means on the ver
on the verge of
going so you should learn that word uh k
why is it important in the study of
subtle
agitation uh a thought about something
you'd like to do is just about to
happen Okay okay you got to try to get
the what that feels like deep into
meditation your mind would like to have
a thought about lunch in about 3 seconds
and and you feel it under the ice you
see the mind is headed towards the
thought about lunch and it's going to
pop out from under the ice okay and then
subtle agitation
means you're on the kit you're on the
verge of having a thought about lunch
and you got to be fast enough to catch
it and stop it ahead of time that's
really cool right like
you you you you prevent you you
proactively prevent a thought about
lunch 3 seconds before it was going to
come out and that's blocking subtle
agitation
so uh that gets pretty cool you you
sense a thought coming and you block it
okay you sense a thought about lunch
coming and you block it
so we're I think we're on to level
six uh which is right here
okay it's
22 and it's called sh cha
okay uh Sha Sha in tibetan means Shanti
it means peace okay shaa means to quiet
the mind okay to quiet the
mind I don't know if you remember but in
the last one which was at
21 the the
dude uh was having uh subtle dullness
and he sank tiad to be to get his mind
out of the subtle dullness
yeah he uplifted his mind it can be any
kind of inspiring or thing you know it
can be any any inspiring thing you can
even do it with a sex thought okay right
if your mind is in subtle dullness and
you just can't get out of it then think
of some sexy guy and it will go whoop
and then uh then go to a meaningful
update okay uh but you can uplift the
mind with almost anything just something
very interesting to you intriguing to
you start with virtuous things if it
doesn't work you can try with other
things okay uh but I've tried it it
works okay uh so you can bring your you
can bring your mind
up then then we we've been talking about
the driving the car metaphor right and
what's going to happen when you you
know bring the guy up you know it's
going to go overboard it's like a
pendulum thing it's always like a
pendulum you know you you get subtle
dness so you think of some guy and then
the pentalum swings back and then it
goes too far and then you have to grab
it and bring it back again with a
different kind of thought so at at
uh number 22 at the sixth level there is
a subtle the danger of subtle
agitation which was triggered by over s
toing okay okay over saying over
uplifting the Mind by this point is
extremely subtle okay like you should
have thought
about
uh you should have thought about how
lucky you are for about 6 seconds and
you thought about it for 8 seconds okay
we're talking subtle here and then it
took you over into you know I really am
the best person in the room you know and
then uh you went a little too far
and that became subtle agitation all
right
okay
but and and here I'm giving you uh
something for your homework assignment
right the
danger and the what do you call it
duration the danger and the duration of
subtle
agitation at 22 is less than at 21 and
that's that's partly why 22 is divided
from 21 okay controlling the mind at
controlling the mind the danger and
duration of subtle a
subtle dullness sorry of subtle
agitation is
is less than it is at the next
sorry at 22 the danger and dur duration
of subtle agitation is less than a21
okay and that's what distinguishes them
and that's why they split them into
two
okay by the end of Step
22 by the end of Step
22 uh your shin Z okay
Z which means the power of your capacity
to catch your
mind making an error in meditation is
fully developed okay it's fully
developed Your Capacity to catch
yourself uh wandering in your meditation
somehow right having D having agitation
having dullness or having subtle dness
or having
no by the time you get to 22 your sh is
fully developed it's it's it's totally
mature and fully powerful and that's why
the guy is holding
up the hook okay
remember his right hand has the hook of
of watchfulness right remember we had
the name for it was down the very first
thing uh sorry yeah number three down at
the beginning was identifying his hook
as his capacity to catch himself losing
it in his meditation okay and and now up
in 22 that hook is he's got the hook up
in the air it means my my Shan is now I
got real sh finally I can really catch
my mind doing anything okay at any
time so we would call Shan the impetus
for those two levels you see level five
and level six the impetus for them or
the power remember we had six Powers
which one are we on God
knows uh but
anyway uh Shin is the power there let's
go backwards and see before that we had
Duma for the previous two which was
bringing the Mind back before that we
had uh SAA which was considering your
llama's instructions and before that we
had Tia which was hearing your llama's
instructions so how many we got four
power now we have hearing your llama's
instructions which is how we got to to
meditation level number one we have
considering your llama's instructions
which is how we got to meditation level
number two we have being able F being
fully able to bring the Mind back to its
object which was characterized levels
three and
four and now we have a fully developed
capacity to catch ourselves making boo
boos in meditation which characteriz
Rises levels five and six okay so we
have four powers out of four powers out
of six are taken care of
okay and then we're ready to go
to um level 7's going to be up here at
24 okay and there's a bit of a story
about level seven so we're not going to
do it tonight cuz you're already late
for
dinner uh
okay so we'll start on that tomorrow
morning we'll get on to level seven and
and we'll see what's happening between 6
and
7 if you have a did we get
tubes can can we get tubes yeah it's
really bad karma to abuse a poster so
we'll try to get tubes by
tomorrow after afternoon or
something and I and last thing I'd like
to say is that
uh all
right it's like rain on a
10 please be in the mood in the mode of
teaching this okay please listen with
the idea that I'm going to teach this
okay that's what I'm I really really
want to see I want to see this big uh
proliferation of this meditation poster
teaching it's fantastic there's nothing
like it you know uh it's a really huge
contribution you can make to the world
you know you can get yoga almost
anywhere now you go to Shanghai and
there's already there's three yoga
studios on the Block you know even in
Shang not I was in Taipei I gave a talk
at the first Yoga Studio in Taipei three
or four years ago now there's a yoga
studio on every block and the kids at
that studio are all on shabi Joy's
Series 2 and ripping it and I would made
the mistake of going in there to take a
class uh and these are the people I
turned on to yoga like four years ago
and I it was a shame I was ashamed you
know and they're like ripping it you
know like Chinese people have a
discipline
uh so anyway I'd like to see that happen
with the poster you know I'd like to
walk into a a yoga you can get yoga
anywhere and it's pretty good anywhere
but but meditation is a is just what do
you call it it's like all it's bogus and
somebody says you know calm your mind
and think about nothing and you know
like really bogus stuff there's no uh
what do you call
authentic uh tradition of meditation
which has been spread the yoga poses are
authentic almost any studio in the world
the poses are authentic which is just
some kind of good karma that we have uh
but the meditation is is bizarre you
know so I would really love to see you
be at the core of a ground zero and and
then see this correct and very
helpful uh teachings on meditation very
ancient teachings that they that they
just become part of every other Studio
you know 10 15 years from now they just
take it for granted they don't even know
where it came from which is the best way
to do a good deed you're just
transparent you know they don't remember
where it came from but all the studios
you know they're they're like meditation
level seven class tonight you know and
they check you before you come
in I would like to see that so you guys
got to do it okay you guys got to learn
it right and and as you go through the
next four or five days you go through it
with the idea that I got to get this
down right uh cuz I got to pass it on
don't be the schmuck in 2 and a half
thousand years that passes it on wrong
okay who makes a mistake okay after all
those years you know you at Friendly
Pines
Camp you know you you you screwed up
level six
you know what I mean okay that's not
very friendly